David Stick Papers PC.5001
State Archives of North Carolina
- Organizations and Agencies, 1930-2009 and undated; 45072; Stick, David, 1919-2009
  - Dare County Tourist Bureau, 1951-1988; 6686; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Dare County Tourist Bureau, 1956; 26555; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Tourist Bureau)
      Includes a document condemning cheating in the Pirates Jamboree Beard Growing Competition and clarifying rules governing beard growth, and several other documents addressed to or relating to the "bearded men" of Dare County.
    - Dare County Tourist Bureau, 1964-1966; 26556; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Tourist Bureau)
    - Financial Statements, 1964-1969; 26557; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Financial Statements)
    - Dare County Tourist Bureau, 1967; 26558; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Tourist Bureau)
    - Accommodations Directory, 1967; 26559; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Accommodations Directory)
    - Board of Directors, 1967; 26560; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Board of Directors)
    - Executive Committee, 1967; 26561; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Executive Committee)
    - Inquiry Lists, 1967; 26562; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Inquiry Lists)
    - Manager - Aycock, 1967; 26563; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Manager - Aycock)
    - Dare County Tourist Bureau, 1968-1969; 26564; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Tourist Bureau)
    - Dare County Tourist Bureau, 1970s; 26565; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Tourist Bureau)
    - Tourist Bureau Speech, 21 November 1980; 26566; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Tourist Bureau Speech)
    - Dare County Tourist Bureau, 1980-1981; 26567; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Tourist Bureau)
    - Dare County Tourist Bureau, 1982-1984; 26568; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Tourist Bureau)
    - Dare County Tourist Bureau, 1985-1988; 26569; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Tourist Bureau)
  - Friends of the Lost Colony, 1958-1959; 6687; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    The Dare County Friends of the Lost Colony was founded in 1959 to assist with fundraising efforts to support the Lost Colony drama, which was suffering a decline in sales. The organization existed for less than a year. This subseries contains correspondence, meeting minutes, and other foundational documents related to the group.
    - Friends of the Lost Colony, 1959; 26570; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Friends of the Lost Colony)
    - Dare County Day, Fort Raleigh, 1959; 26571; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dare County Day, Fort Raleigh)
    - Roanoke Island Historical Association, 1958; 26572; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Roanoke Island Historical Association)
    - Roanoke Island Historical Association, 1959; 26573; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Roanoke Island Historical Association)
    - The Colony Callboard (News from the Lost Colony), 1959; 26574; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder The Colony Callboard (News from the Lost Colony))
    - Roanoke Island Historical Association Report on Audit, 1959; 26575; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Roanoke Island Historical Association Report on Audit)
  - Historical Society of North Carolina, 1957-1990; 6688; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    - Card Index of Authors, circa 1969; 26576; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Card Index of Authors)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1985; 26577; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
    - Historical Society of North Carolina, 1957-1963; 26578; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Historical Society of North Carolina)
    - Historical Society of North Carolina, 1987-1989; 26579; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Historical Society of North Carolina)
    - Research Material [3 folders], 1959-1987; 26580; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Research Material [3 folders])
    - Historical Society of North Carolina, 1990; 26581; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Historical Society of North Carolina)
  - Joint Telephone Committee, 1947-1956; 6689; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    The Joint Telephone Committee was organized at the behest of David Stick to improve telephone services throughout the Outer Banks in the early 1950s. This subseries primarily includes correspondence between stick and various telephone companies and individuals related to telephone services.
    - Telephones, 1948; 26582; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Telephones)
    - Telephones, 1949; 26583; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Telephones)
    - Telephones, 1950; 26584; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Telephones)
    - Telephones, 1951-1953; 26585; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Telephones)
    - Telephones, 1954; 26586; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Telephones)
    - Telephones, 1955; 26587; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Telephones)
    - Telephones, 1956; 26588; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Telephones)
    - Telephones - Miscellaneous, 1947-1955; 26589; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Telephones - Miscellaneous)
  - Kitty Hawk Civic Club, 1948-1951; 6690; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kitty Hawk Civic Club)
  - Marine Resources Center Citizens' Advisory Council, 1969-1984; 6691; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    The Marine Resources Center was founded on the north end of Roanoke Island. In 1986 it was renamed the North Carolina Aquarium at Roanoke Island, and as of 2019, it continues to operate under than name. The materials in this subseries related to the Marine Resources Center's Citizens' Advisory Council, a group of local constituents who assisted the aquarium in an advisory role.
    - Citizens Advisory Committee, 1979-1983; 26590; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Citizens Advisory Committee)
    - Incorporation through Open Meeting, 1982; 26591; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Incorporation through Open Meeting)
    - Monthly Reports, 1981-1984; 26592; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Monthly Reports)
    - Printed Material, 1977-1983; 26593; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Printed Material)
    - Personal Notes, 1969-1982; 26594; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Personal Notes)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1983; 26595; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
  - North Carolina Coastal Resources Commission (CRC), 1969-1987 and undated; 6692; Stick, David, 1919-2009
    The federal Coastal Zone Management Act, passed in 1972, mandated an exploration into solving mounting problems along the United States coast. The North Carolina legislature responded by introducing the Coastal Area Management Act (CAMA) in the 1973 General Assembly session. The bill was met with a great deal of opposition across the state, and it was not passed until 1975. The bill granted authority to a gubernatorially-appointed 15-member board called the Coastal Resources Commission (CRC) to make policy decisions affecting coastal zone management. David Stick was one of the appointees to the commission. CAMA was designed to provide a program for the protection, preservation, orderly development, and management of North Carolina's coastal resources. It affected 20 eastern North Carolina Counties. The CRC was charged with developing state guidelines that would allow each county and municipality in the region to create its own land use plan incorporating public input. Each plan classified its land area into five categories: developed, transition, community, rural, and conservation. The CRC conducted continuing studies on coastal zone management in the region and made regular reports to the General Assembly. The group also identified areas in need of preservation and designated them as Areas of Environmental Concern, or AECs, which required a special permit before any development activity could be undertaken. CAMA is considered to have been an extremely volatile and controversial law, with environmentalists describing it as too lenient and developers calling it too restrictive. The North Carolina Coastal Resources Commission subseries is the largest in the Organizations and Agencies series, and contains extensive documentation of developments regarding CAMA, activities of the CRC, and public input into the process. Included are drafts and published versions of legislative acts related to coastal zone management, data gathered and speeches given by Stick in support of the bill, information on the members of the CRC, public relations material generated by the CRC, meeting minutes and agendas, correspondence, and other records related to CAMA and the CRC. Included are drafts and published copies of land use plans (occasionally including related material, such as correspondence and notes) created by North Carolina counties and municipalities using guidelines issued by the CRC.
    - Coastal Resources Commission Data, 1974; 26596; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Resources Commission Data)
    - Coastal Resources Commission Material for Mike, 1976; 26597; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Resources Commission Material for Mike)
    - Coastal Zone Management in North Carolina - Synopses and Reviews, 1976-1977; 26598; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Zone Management in North Carolina - Synopses and Reviews)
    - Background Information compiled by the Office of Marine Affairs [3 folders], undated; 26599; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Background Information compiled by the Office of Marine Affairs [3 folders])
    - Coastal Area Management Act, 1969-1987; 6790; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Pre-CAMA, 1972-1976; 6791; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Federal Coastal Zone Management Act, 1972-1973; 26600; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Federal Coastal Zone Management Act)
        - Excluded Federal Lands Under CZMA, 1972-1976; 26601; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Excluded Federal Lands Under CZMA)
        - Various Federal Laws and Regulations, 1972; 26602; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Various Federal Laws and Regulations)
        - CAMA Precursors in North Carolina, 1972-1974; 26603; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder CAMA Precursors in North Carolina)
        - Coastal Area Management Hearing, 18 April 1973; 26604; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Area Management Hearing)
        - Coastal Area Land Management Hearing, 20 August 1973; 26605; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Area Land Management Hearing)
        - Coastal Area Land Management Seminar, 10 October 1973; 26606; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Area Land Management Seminar)
        - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974; 26607; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
        - Personal, 1974; 26608; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Personal)
      - Board of Realtors Speech, 1973; 6792; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Text, 1973; 26609; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Text)
        - Reactions, 1973; 26610; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Reactions)
        - Correspondence, 1973; 26611; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
      - CAMA and Related Acts, 1969-1977; 6793; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - CAMA Text, 1973; 26612; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder CAMA Text)
        - Executive Order Designating Coastal Counties, 1974; 26613; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Executive Order Designating Coastal Counties)
        - Informal Analysis (D. Stick), 1974; 26614; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Informal Analysis (D. Stick))
        - Notes for Informal Analysis (D. Stick), 1974; 26615; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Notes for Informal Analysis (D. Stick))
        - Amendment to CAMA, 1975; 26616; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Amendment to CAMA)
        - Amendments to CAMA, 1977; 26617; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Amendments to CAMA)
        - Legal Challenges - Adams et. al. vs. NCDNER et. al. - Defendants' Brief, 1977; 26618; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Legal Challenges - Adams et. al. vs. NCDNER et. al. - Defendants' Brief)
        - Legal Challenges - Adams et. al. vs. NCDNER et. al. - Plaintiffs' Brief, 1977; 26619; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Legal Challenges - Adams et. al. vs. NCDNER et. al. - Plaintiffs' Brief)
        - Legal Challenges - Adams et. al. vs. NCDNER et. al. - Miscellaneous, 1977; 26620; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Legal Challenges - Adams et. al. vs. NCDNER et. al. - Miscellaneous)
        - Other Legal Challenges, 1976; 26621; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Other Legal Challenges)
        - Mountain Area Management Act, 1975; 26622; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Mountain Area Management Act)
        - Administrative Procedures Act, 1976; 26623; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Administrative Procedures Act)
        - Linton Study Act etc., 1969; 26624; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Linton Study Act etc.)
      - Personal, 1973-1987; 6794; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Basic Information Sheet, 1977; 26625; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Basic Information Sheet)
        - Commission Problems, June 1975; 26626; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Commission Problems)
        - Correspondence, 1977; 26627; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence)
        - Expenses, David Stick, 1974-1977; 26628; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Expenses, David Stick)
        - Handbook on Public Participation, 1975-1975; 26629; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Handbook on Public Participation)
        - Handbook for Public Participation (Background Information), 1973-1975; 26630; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Handbook for Public Participation (Background Information))
        - Coastal Resources Commission (Miscellaneous Writings), 1974-1987; 26631; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Resources Commission (Miscellaneous Writings))
        - Nominations, Oath of Office, and Resignations, 1976-1977; 26632; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Nominations, Oath of Office, and Resignations)
      - Speeches, 1974-1976; 6795; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Albemarle Regional Planning and Development Commission, 1974; 26633; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Albemarle Regional Planning and Development Commission)
        - Conference on Marine Resources of the Coastal Plain, Wilmington, 1974; 26634; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Conference on Marine Resources of the Coastal Plain, Wilmington)
        - North Carolina Society of Engineers, Durham, 1975; 26635; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Society of Engineers, Durham)
        - UNC Sea Grant Forum, 1975; 26636; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder UNC Sea Grant Forum)
        - Miscellaneous, 1975-1976; 26637; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
    - Coastal Resources Commission, 1970-1987 and undated; 6796; Stick, David, 1919-2009
      - Commission Members, 1974-1977; 6797; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Chesson, Parker, 1974-1975; 26638; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Chesson, Parker)
        - Committee Assignments, 1974-1976; 26639; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Committee Assignments)
        - Darden, DeWitt, 1974; 26640; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Darden, DeWitt)
        - Davis, Walter, 1976; 26641; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Davis, Walter)
        - Eure, Tom, 1974-1977; 26642; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Eure, Tom)
        - Furlough, Frank, 1977; 26643; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Furlough, Frank)
        - Haste, Erie, 1976; 26644; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Haste, Erie)
        - Jernigan, Roberts, 1976; 26645; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Jernigan, Roberts)
        - Kopp, Bill, 1975; 26646; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Kopp, Bill)
        - Lancaster, Glenn, 1974; 26647; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Lancaster, Glenn)
        - Membership, General, 1974; 26648; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Membership, General)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1974-1977; 26649; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous Correspondence)
        - Powell, Doug, 1974-1977; 26650; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Powell, Doug)
        - Smith, Axson, 1974; 26651; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Smith, Axson)
        - Smith, L.D., 1975; 26652; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Smith, L.D.)
        - Wells, Charles, 1976-1977; 26653; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wells, Charles)
      - Other Individuals, 1974-1987; 6798; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Cooper, Art, 1974-1976; 26654; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Cooper, Art)
        - Dawson, Amos, 1976; 26655; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Dawson, Amos)
        - Harrington, James, 1974-1975; 26656; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Harrington, James)
        - Hecker, Stan, 1974-1975; 26657; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hecker, Stan)
        - Holshouser, Governor James E. Jr., 1974; 26658; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Holshouser, Governor James E. Jr.)
        - Hunt, Jim, 1975-1977; 26659; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Hunt, Jim)
        - Correspondence - Staff, 1975-1977; 26660; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Correspondence - Staff)
        - Whichard, Willis, 1977-1987; 26661; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Whichard, Willis)
      - Other Organizations and Agencies, 1974-1976; 6799; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Albemarle Association of Counties and Towns, 1975; 26662; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Albemarle Association of Counties and Towns)
        - Albemarle Regional Planning and Development Commission, 1974; 26663; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Albemarle Regional Planning and Development Commission)
        - Coastal Plains Center for Marine Development Services, 1974; 26664; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Plains Center for Marine Development Services)
        - Coastal Plains Regional Commission, 1974; 26665; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Plains Regional Commission)
        - Coastal Resources Advisory Council, 1974-1976; 26666; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal Resources Advisory Council)
        - Coastal States Organization, 1974; 26667; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastal States Organization)
        - Conservation Council of North Carolina, 1975-1976; 26668; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Conservation Council of North Carolina)
        - Liaison and Coordination Committee for Coastal Area Management Plans and Programs, 1974; 26669; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Liaison and Coordination Committee for Coastal Area Management Plans and Programs)
        - Miscellaneous, 1975; 26670; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
        - North Carolina Agricultural Extension Service, 1976; 26671; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Agricultural Extension Service)
        - North Carolina Department of Natural and Economic Resources, 1975; 26672; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Department of Natural and Economic Resources)
        - North Carolina Department of Natural and Economic Resources: Elizabeth City Office, 1974; 26673; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Department of Natural and Economic Resources: Elizabeth City Office)
        - North Carolina Department of Natural and Economic Resources: Washington Office, 1974; 26674; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Department of Natural and Economic Resources: Washington Office)
        - North Carolina Wildlife Resources Commission, 1974; 26675; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder North Carolina Wildlife Resources Commission)
        - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, 1975; 26676; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder U.S. Army Corps of Engineers)
      - Other States, 1970-1978 and undated; 6800; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - California, 1973; 26677; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder California)
        - Delaware, undated; 26678; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Delaware)
        - Florida, 1971-1974; 26679; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Florida)
        - Louisiana, 1977; 26680; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Louisiana)
        - Maine, 1972; 26681; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Maine)
        - Michigan, 1970; 26682; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Michigan)
        - New Jersey, 1976; 26683; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder New Jersey)
        - Oregon, 1974; 26684; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Oregon)
        - Virginia, 1973-1978; 26685; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Virginia)
        - Washington, 1971-1972; 26686; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Washington)
      - Public Relations, 1973-1982; 6801; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Citizen Involvement Project - Urban Institute, 1976; 26687; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Citizen Involvement Project - Urban Institute)
        - Coastland Times, 1974-1975; 26688; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastland Times)
        - Coastline, 1975; 26689; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Coastline)
        - Miscellaneous, 1974-1977; 26690; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Miscellaneous)
        - News and Observer Article, 1977; 26691; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder News and Observer Article)
        - Public Participation Coordinators, 1976; 26692; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Public Participation Coordinators)
        - Rann Proposal, 1974; 26693; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Rann Proposal)
        - Sea Grant Newsletter Debate, 1977; 26694; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Sea Grant Newsletter Debate)
        - Speeches, 1975; 26695; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Speeches)
        - Speeches, Testimony, etc., 1973-1982; 26696; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Speeches, Testimony, etc.)
        - WITN-TV 7, 1975; 26697; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder WITN-TV 7)
        - WVEC-TV 13, 1975; 26698; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder WVEC-TV 13)
        - Warren, Betsy, 1974-1975; 26699; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Warren, Betsy)
      - Commission Meetings, 1974-1977; 6802; Stick, David, 1919-2009
        - Organizational Meeting, Morehead, 1974; 26700; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Organizational Meeting, Morehead)
        - Wilmington, 1974; 26701; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wilmington)
        - Elizabeth City, 1974; 26702; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Elizabeth City)
        - New Bern, 1974; 26703; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder New Bern)
        - New Bern, 1974; 26704; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder New Bern)
        - New Bern, 1974; 26705; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder New Bern)
        - Wrightsville Beach, 1975; 26706; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wrightsville Beach)
        - Belhaven, 1975; 26707; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Belhaven)
        - Craven Community College, 1975; 26708; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Craven Community College)
        - Raleigh, 1975; 26709; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Raleigh)
        - Nags Head, 1975; 26710; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Nags Head)
        - Morehead City, 1975; 26711; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Morehead City)
        - Washington, 1975; 26712; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Washington)
        - Pine Knoll Shores, 1975; 26713; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Pine Knoll Shores)
        - Nags Head, 1975; 26714; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Nags Head)
        - Raleigh [2 Folders], 1975; 26715; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Raleigh [2 Folders])
        - Raleigh, 1976; 26716; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Raleigh)
        - Wrightsville Beach, 1976; 26717; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wrightsville Beach)
        - New Bern, 1976; 26718; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder New Bern)
        - Raleigh, 1976; 26719; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Raleigh)
        - New Bern, 1976; 26720; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder New Bern)
        - Pine Knoll Shores, 1976; 26721; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Pine Knoll Shores)
        - Raleigh, 1976; 26722; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Raleigh)
        - Wilmington, 1976; 26723; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Wilmington)
        - Raleigh, 1976; 26724; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Raleigh)
        - Nags Head, 1976; 26725; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Nags Head)
        - New Bern, 1976; 26726; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder New Bern)
        - New Bern, 1976; 26727; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder New Bern)
        - Raleigh, 1977; 26728; Stick, David, 1919-2009 (Folder Raleigh)